<resources>
    <string name="app_name">happie gardener</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="tick_mark">tick</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


    <string name="handprunercutter">
        Material:Stainless Steel, Color:Colorful
Package Contents:1 Pc Pruner Cutter
Quality Plastic material body and Steel handles, quality blade made of high carbon steel with Ultra-fine Polishing Technology
    </string>
    
    <string name="handtoolkit">
        3 PC Gardening Tools Kit: Perfect for digging, weeding, transplanting and cultivating. The most useful gardening tools for yourself or a person who loves gardening.
Package Content: 3 Pcs Garden tools (Hand Cultivator, Trowel, Transplanter)
Material and Size: Iron, 17 x 4.5 cm + 17 x 3.3 cm + 15 x 4.5 cm
    </string>

    <string name="bonsai">
        Choose the Right Tree: Pick a tree suitable for your climate and space.
Select a Bonsai Pot: Use a well-draining pot with holes.
Use Proper Soil: Opt for well-draining bonsai soil.
Regular Repotting: Repot every 2-3 years for optimal growth.
    </string>
<string name="variety45">
    Please make sure you are buying original "ONLY FOR ORGANIC" brand products which is sold by "ONLY FOR ORGANIC"
Best in class germination, Suitable for all Seasons, Fresh Seeds.
Growing Instructions Inside The Box
</string>
    <string name="combo6">
        PACKAGE CONTENTS : 6 Packet of Vegetable Seeds | 1 Packet Brinjal Long Seeds | 1 Packet Capsicum Green Seeds | 1 Packet Cauliflower Seeds | 1 Packet Chilli Long Seeds | 1 Packet Coriander Seeds | 1 Packet Tomato Seeds
EASY TO GROW VEGETABLES COMBO : Combo includes exotic vegetables which can be grown in indian climate/weather conditions during Aug to Feb months
    </string>
    <string name="lavender">
        Packages Include :- 1 Pcs Artificial Flowers with Plastic Pot, Material : Plastic, Size : 10 cm x 7 cm, Color : Multi
Versatile Decorative Objects : Our fake flowers in pot can be used as end table decor or desk decor. The artificial potted flowers can also go on shelves anywhere in your home or in the office!
Low-Maintenance Potted Plants : Unlike real, live plants, our fake plant require no maintenance. No need to worry about watering the lavender plants to keep them thriving!
    </string>

    <string name="Bamboo_feng">
        One of the most popular indoor plant that is easy to care for making it a perfect plant for home decor.
Bamboo plant according to Feng Shui is said to bring good luck and prosperity to your home
Watering is simple for the Lucky bamboo plant. Water must be changed after every 3-4 days for better growth.
    </string>
    <string name="orchid">
        Package consist of one healthy, live, tissue cultured dendrobium plant
Plants will be in 3.5 inch orchid pot with hanger and potting material
Living Colours Farm Orchid Care Fertilizer 50 gm in the pack to take care of plants
Plants provided in pot with chemically treated potting material to avoid fungus
All plants will be labelled with names
    </string>

    <string name="Desertrose">
        Taking care and growing adenium obesum, a succulent plant more commonly known as Desert Rose
Desert Rose plants found at the garden shop are usually grown from seed and similar to the true species found in nature.
    </string>
</resources>